{
  "exams": [
    {
      "id": 1768957424037,
      "title": "GK",
      "duration": 10,
      "totalMarks": 7,
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1768957410048,
          "type": "mcq",
          "text": "What is the capital of France?",
          "options": [
            "London",
            "Berlin",
            "Paris",
            "Madrid"
          ],
          "correct": "Paris",
          "marks": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 1768957413442,
          "type": "truefalse",
          "text": "JS is awesome.",
          "correct": true,
          "marks": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 1768957415814,
          "type": "short",
          "text": "www",
          "answer": "www",
          "marks": 5
        }
      ],
      "createdBy": "instructor@test.com",
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T01:03:45.536Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 1768957884092,
      "title": "English",
      "duration": 10,
      "totalMarks": 9,
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1768957785659,
          "type": "mcq",
          "text": "he   football.",
          "options": [
            "play",
            "plays",
            "played",
            "playing"
          ],
          "correct": "plays",
          "marks": 3
        },
        {
          "id": 1768957819847,
          "type": "truefalse",
          "text": "he is watching tennis. is correct grammer?",
          "correct": true,
          "marks": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 1768957854985,
          "type": "short",
          "text": "who stands for",
          "answer": "world health organization",
          "marks": 5
        }
      ],
      "createdBy": "instructor@test.com",
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T01:11:25.490Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 1768969785337,
      "title": "Matths",
      "duration": 10,
      "totalMarks": 10,
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1768969677529,
          "type": "mcq",
          "text": "2+2 is ",
          "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
          ],
          "correct": "4",
          "marks": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 1768969707306,
          "type": "truefalse",
          "text": "34-4 is 29",
          "correct": false,
          "marks": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 1768969731610,
          "type": "short",
          "text": "3*4",
          "answer": "12",
          "marks": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 1768969747719,
          "type": "numeric",
          "text": "12/4",
          "correct": 3,
          "marks": 1
        }
      ],
      "createdBy": "instructor@test.com",
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T04:29:46.990Z"
    }
  ],
  "submissions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "examId": 1,
      "examTitle": "English",
      "studentName": "jo",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768955803582,
          "questionText": "he __football.",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "plays",
          "correctAnswer": "plays",
          "marks": 3,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768955844638,
          "questionText": "football has most funs than cricket. is this correct in grammer?",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": true,
          "correctAnswer": true,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768955892381,
          "questionText": "www stands for",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "worl wide web",
          "correctAnswer": "worl wide web",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": true
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T00:39:07.116Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T00:39:29.860Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768955803582": 5,
          "1768955844638": 7,
          "1768955892381": 6
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 1,
        "visibilityEvents": []
      },
      "totalMarks": 9,
      "awarded": 7,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T00:39:29.868Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "examId": 1768957424037,
      "examTitle": "GK",
      "studentName": "ora",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768957410048,
          "questionText": "What is the capital of France?",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "Paris",
          "correctAnswer": "Paris",
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957413442,
          "questionText": "JS is awesome.",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": false,
          "correctAnswer": true,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 0,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957415814,
          "questionText": "www",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "www",
          "correctAnswer": "www",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": false
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T01:04:39.061Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T01:04:56.062Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768957410048": 6,
          "1768957413442": 4,
          "1768957415814": 3
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 0,
        "visibilityEvents": []
      },
      "totalMarks": 7,
      "awarded": 6,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T01:04:56.087Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "examId": 1768957884092,
      "examTitle": "English",
      "studentName": "soal",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768957785659,
          "questionText": "he   football.",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "plays",
          "correctAnswer": "plays",
          "marks": 3,
          "awarded": 3,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957819847,
          "questionText": "he is watching tennis. is correct grammer?",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": true,
          "correctAnswer": true,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957854985,
          "questionText": "who stands for",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "world health organization",
          "correctAnswer": "world health organization",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": false
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T01:12:40.321Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T01:13:17.614Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768957785659": 5,
          "1768957819847": 2,
          "1768957854985": 23
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 0,
        "visibilityEvents": []
      },
      "totalMarks": 9,
      "awarded": 9,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T01:13:17.634Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "examId": 1768957424037,
      "examTitle": "GK",
      "studentName": "soool",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768957410048,
          "questionText": "What is the capital of France?",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "Paris",
          "correctAnswer": "Paris",
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957413442,
          "questionText": "JS is awesome.",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": true,
          "correctAnswer": true,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957415814,
          "questionText": "www",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "www",
          "correctAnswer": "www",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": true
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T01:29:59.751Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T01:30:22.344Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768957410048": 14,
          "1768957413442": 7,
          "1768957415814": 14
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 0,
        "visibilityEvents": [
          {
            "at": "2026-01-21T01:05:11.962Z",
            "visibility": "hidden"
          }
        ]
      },
      "totalMarks": 7,
      "awarded": 7,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T01:30:22.352Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "examId": 1768957884092,
      "examTitle": "English",
      "studentName": "dana",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768957785659,
          "questionText": "he   football.",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "plays",
          "correctAnswer": "plays",
          "marks": 3,
          "awarded": 3,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957819847,
          "questionText": "he is watching tennis. is correct grammer?",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": true,
          "correctAnswer": true,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957854985,
          "questionText": "who stands for",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "world health organization",
          "correctAnswer": "world health organization",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": true
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T01:33:13.785Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T01:33:49.464Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768957785659": 12,
          "1768957819847": 5,
          "1768957854985": 44
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 0,
        "visibilityEvents": [
          {
            "at": "2026-01-21T01:13:37.819Z",
            "visibility": "hidden"
          },
          {
            "at": "2026-01-21T01:13:39.670Z",
            "visibility": "visible"
          },
          {
            "at": "2026-01-21T01:13:42.925Z",
            "visibility": "hidden"
          }
        ]
      },
      "totalMarks": 9,
      "awarded": 9,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T01:33:49.490Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 1768969857669,
      "examId": 1768969785337,
      "examTitle": "Matths",
      "studentName": "ezana",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768969677529,
          "questionText": "2+2 is ",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "4",
          "correctAnswer": "4",
          "marks": 2,
          "awarded": 2,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768969707306,
          "questionText": "34-4 is 29",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": false,
          "marks": 2,
          "awarded": 2,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768969731610,
          "questionText": "3*4",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "12",
          "correctAnswer": "12",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768969747719,
          "questionText": "12/4",
          "type": "numeric",
          "studentAnswer": "3",
          "correctAnswer": 3,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T04:30:30.694Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T04:30:57.659Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768969677529": 10,
          "1768969707306": 4,
          "1768969731610": 5,
          "1768969747719": 5
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 0,
        "visibilityEvents": []
      },
      "totalMarks": 10,
      "awarded": 10,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T04:30:57.669Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 1768979297811,
      "examId": 1768969785337,
      "examTitle": "Matths",
      "studentName": "jhon",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768969677529,
          "questionText": "2+2 is ",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "4",
          "correctAnswer": "4",
          "marks": 2,
          "awarded": 2,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768969707306,
          "questionText": "34-4 is 29",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": true,
          "marks": 2,
          "awarded": 0,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768969731610,
          "questionText": "3*4",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "12",
          "correctAnswer": "12",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768969747719,
          "questionText": "12/4",
          "type": "numeric",
          "studentAnswer": "2",
          "correctAnswer": 3,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 0,
          "autoGraded": true
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T07:07:53.042Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T07:08:17.763Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768969677529": 17,
          "1768969707306": 10,
          "1768969731610": 8,
          "1768969747719": 14
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 0,
        "visibilityEvents": [
          {
            "at": "2026-01-21T04:31:10.765Z",
            "visibility": "hidden"
          }
        ]
      },
      "totalMarks": 10,
      "awarded": 7,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T07:08:17.811Z"
    },
    {
      "id": 1768980018952,
      "examId": 1768957424037,
      "examTitle": "GK",
      "studentName": "zooma",
      "perQuestion": [
        {
          "questionId": 1768957410048,
          "questionText": "What is the capital of France?",
          "type": "mcq",
          "studentAnswer": "Paris",
          "correctAnswer": "Paris",
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957413442,
          "questionText": "JS is awesome.",
          "type": "truefalse",
          "studentAnswer": true,
          "correctAnswer": true,
          "marks": 1,
          "awarded": 1,
          "autoGraded": true
        },
        {
          "questionId": 1768957415814,
          "questionText": "www",
          "type": "short",
          "studentAnswer": "www",
          "correctAnswer": "www",
          "marks": 5,
          "awarded": 5,
          "autoGraded": true
        }
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "startedAt": "2026-01-21T07:19:54.563Z",
        "endedAt": "2026-01-21T07:20:18.944Z",
        "durationSeconds": 600,
        "perQuestionTimes": {
          "1768957410048": 22,
          "1768957413442": 10,
          "1768957415814": 25
        },
        "tabSwitchCount": 0,
        "visibilityEvents": [
          {
            "at": "2026-01-21T01:30:31.830Z",
            "visibility": "hidden"
          }
        ]
      },
      "totalMarks": 7,
      "awarded": 7,
      "createdAt": "2026-01-21T07:20:18.952Z"
    }
  ],
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "email": "instructor@test.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$m7ZC0crHMrHaQDUvTOOFyOFnyNWH20wS9kNJtmekWG.0.PA0iWlT2",
      "role": "instructor"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "email": "student@test.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$pz.8aqXD/8D1js7IMruj.OjDjRRdVYKZvdo41A9yYIwND/dOS03hO",
      "role": "student"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "email": "grader@test.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$RZZyKvkQmEYMMaqQUoXwKOapfyOfORUk.BQ8g4/Ps4HEU/u7zvyQ.",
      "role": "grader"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "email": "admin@test.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$fCLaYNsvWnzlpxLagxvjVuKu4s/W8e5NI/zXinhP4IE.mBU3KROGy",
      "role": "admin"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "email": "newuser@test.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$EsN8JBlCl7qlJ1DZ3JoGgOAU3m2dINtRkxq6loqCRdNw48LMjIr0.",
      "role": "student"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "email": "kalilhida24@gmail.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$a1RaILGJXgF/.c642IaXVuR5ngsFVidDpfMK6QrTEaag8dlhKRgJm",
      "role": "student"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "email": "uiuser@test.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$3QAh6LoDM5NcH9ZGh.76du4GWnqBRCuPUOrgNNpPR9kMB7SO5Vr96",
      "role": "student"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "email": "fixuser@test.com",
      "password": "$2b$10$lyrlp5pTstkTG4DBPqmXtuzWqIPKI8ZHhUr8MXge5U6JRR4tOy/Ly",
      "role": "instructor"
    }
  ]
}